Okay, so the ECC team's top tips for webcam, so each of us have put together
just a few
of our top tips or whatever ones we're thinking about at the moment to help you
to make the
most out of your webcam experience, please, if you have any of your own tips,
anyone that's
watching this, please let us know either in the chat box on here, or if you're
watching
it back in the group on the WhatsApp's, it's great if we can just all learn
from each other
isn't it, and share our tips and advice and support each other. So, also if you
're watching
this call live at the end, if you want to ask us any questions about anything
we've talked
about or anything else at all, then feel free to do that. And you've put your
questions
in the chat as well. So as we go along, we'll keep an eye on the chat just to
see if there's
any questions there. So we'll get started, shall we? So just a few things that
we'll cover
in this call. So we'll cover a little bit about these topics many more. So
phone chat,
free chat, keeping clients for longer, making more money, managing consent and
more. So
Georgia, over to you for your top tips. Hi everyone. So I was just actually
saying to
Elvie the day that my top tips, feel as though I've said it all so many times.
And I was like,
oh, people are probably bored ahead on what I've got to say. But I think
everyone here is new,
which is good. So yeah, I don't think you've heard what I've got to say. But
with that being said,
these are my top tips that I've stuck to most of them for the past 11 years.
And it's always
worked for me. And even though I've been repeating myself so much on the
training,
it's because it works. And it's because, you know, it's not like you need to be
trying all
these new things. It is good to try new things. Don't get me wrong. If there's
a new idea or a new
style of webcam or whatever you want to try, that's great. Both sticking to the
core basics
and, you know, building your profile are it really helps. So I'm going to go
through some of my top tips.
So number one is your webcam setup. I say this a lot. I talk about this a lot
in the chats and
stuff as well. And actually, as well, before we start, if anyone needs to go
grab a pen and
paper, this might be a good time to do it now. Or you can just jot things down
on your laptop.
And so, yeah, so the webcam setup. So obviously, you know, there as much as you
need to be
engaging with your conversation, they still want to see you as well. So make
sure you've got good
lighting. You can buy ring lights. You can buy small little portable lights
like these.
That me and El both have on Amazon and they go nice and bright. So it makes a
real difference
when you're on cam. So you can just pop it right on the front of your laptop
there. And as you can
see, you can see me a lot clearer now with the light. And, yeah, just a space
around you. You
want it to be nice and open and inviting. Not too much clutter going on. You
just want it to look
really presentable, you know, depending on what you do on cam, you might want
to place some objects
around you, around the room. That might, you know, inspire some thought in your
clients. They might
see the objects and think, Oh, I wonder if she will use that. I wonder, you
know, and you can have
that then it can become a conversation piece. And while on the subject of what
's in your background
as well, I'll just mention, and you kind of have any photos in the background,
no animals and no
other people. So as you can see here, exactly how mine is is great because
nothing else can be seen
other than me. And if you do have stuff like that, I'll work, don't make it.
And they will,
they'll give you a little warning. So yeah, best to just keep it nice and clear
.
And then finally, with the webcam setup and your webcam. So if the one on your
laptop seems to be
blurry, you can always invest a little and buy a plug-in. But these days, most
of the laptops come
with a quite a clear cam. So you should be fine with the one you've got. So
yeah, just taking a look
at your webcam setup is quite important, I think. And okay, so I'm going to go
next onto a little
bit about the profile. So your webcam profile is also super important because
this is what the
clients are going to see, obviously, before they click in to come with you. So
I think a lot of
you here are new, so your profiles might be quite basic and not have much out
of the minute,
which is fine. It's good to have a blank canvas to start from. But then as you
progress, you can
start to write more on your profile. You can ask good for inspiration, ask good
for help.
And yeah, just start to write from there what your interests are, what your
hobbies are,
what type of person you are, or the person that you're presenting yourself on
there. This can
just be a fantasy, it doesn't have to be any real information. Of course, we'd
keep any sensitive
information away from there always. And yeah, just spend some time researching
people on the website,
take a look what other people are writing on theirs, see what feels good to you
to add to yours.
And yeah, I think this can make a big difference. But then once you've got what
you've got,
they've got something that works, then you don't need to think about changing
it all the time.
Once you've got something that's working well for you and bringing those
clients in,
then it's only a matter of just tweaking it here and there and updating it a
little here and there
and adding new pictures every now and again, just to keep it fresh. It's not
like you have to do a
big update all the time, you just need to build your profile and then we can
just add a little
bit here and there. So yeah, it's not something that needs a lot of work
constantly. But yeah,
your profile picture is very important. So sometimes they won't actually click
into your profile,
the clients, but everyone will see your profile photo. So your main one is the
most important one,
obviously the first one that appears because that is what they all see when all
of the clients
will see when you log on. And it's going to be a very small photo on a huge
screen with all of
girls on there here on Cam. So you want to make sure yours is as eye-catching
as possible.
One thing I've noticed some of the members doing, some of our members and also
other members on the
site, they actually put like a box or a frame around the profile photo of a
bright colour.
And I think that does help to really catch people's attention. I know one of
our members Yala does
it and she said since she'd done that, she noticed she got more calls. So yes,
you can have your usual
profile photo and then just add a frame of like a bright pink or a bright
orange or really bright
eye-catching colour. I think the colour for sales is actually yellow. I think
that draws people into
spend as the colour yellow. I should look into that, but maybe you could do that
because I think, you know,
what's the word? Like it kind of tricks people into spending anyway. So you
could try something
like that as well just to make it even more eye-catching. And yeah, with the
profile photo,
you just want to make sure that you're taking up as much of the photo as
possible. So full body
ones from far, far away, probably not going to work as well. As a nice close-up
, nice smile or
nice inviting face, you know, look really, try and really engage in this photo.
This is the most
important one. So just really try and choose the best one where you're really
taking up a lot of
the screen and they can really see you. And we can help if you're not really
sure, you know,
out of your pictures, which one will work best, please just ask us and we can
advise what we think
might work best. And one more thing around the photo and around the profile.
And it's really
good to do admin work around CAM. So replying to your emails, in there you'll
have clients asking
you all kinds of things, maybe things you don't want to do and that's fine. If
they're writing
anything in there, you don't want to reply to them. You don't need to apply to
those people. But
there'll be people in there, you know, that you definitely could connect with.
And you can just
tell them, you can respond back to them a little bit here and there, but you
don't want to spend too
much time on emails if they're not coming into your private chat or group chat,
because you will get
free loaders in the email too. But it's definitely worth sending back and forth
a couple of emails
in the beginning to try and convince them to come to your private chat. So, you
know, when you log
on CAM and you're waiting for calls, just click on your emails and just see
what's in there and just
just take five or ten minutes responding to them while you're waiting for calls
. And you can also
send flits on there. So this is a way to connect with new clients. So there's
an option to basically
send them a flit and it's like a little wink kind of thing, like, you know, it
basically just
connect you to the client and then they can potentially email you after that or
come into your private
chat. So again, when you're just sat there waiting for calls, it's good to just
instead of just sat,
you know, watching YouTube or twiddling your phones or whatever, it's good to
just put some
energy and to add up work itself and just take a look at the site, take a look
what you can do,
you know, mess with the profile, send emails, send flits, stuff like that,
honestly does all help.
Okay. So that was tip number one was like a round webcam set up in the profile.
My tip number two is bidding. So for me, bidding has really helped. So some of
you are new here,
so I'll just explain again, just in case you're not sure what it means. But
bidding is basically
just where you pay a couple of credits per minute. Now these credits, they're
not coming out of your
own pocket, they're credits that have already been, you already racked up on
the site. And so you pay
them to position yourself on the front page of the website. So as I said before
, when you log on,
you're just a small little box on a screen with loads of different webcomers on
. And sometimes
you might be on the very back pages. If you bid, you get put to the front page.
And for me,
I've always had good success with bidding whenever I bid and get on the front
page, I notice I get a
lot more calls. But with that being said, I have been speaking to some of my
members about this,
and they actually don't like it. They actually prefer free chat. But I am going
to, it is one of
my top tips because like I said, it has always worked for me. So I would
recommend giving it a go.
You're only going to lose a few credits. You know, if worst comes to worst, if
you don't get any
calls in that hour that you've biddered, you're only going to lose a few
credits. It's not the end
of the world. And yeah, because when you bid, you get put on the front page for
one hour,
I don't know if I already said that. So yeah, I think bidding, you know, really
helps with webcam
traffic. And while on the subject of that, I know I just said that you don't
have to pay the money
out of your own pocket, which you'd really don't. And I myself never have. But
what I actually noticed
is I was going through some of the members, some of our new members, I was
going through their
credit statements, just looking at the payroll and stuff like that. And what I
noticed was
we had quite a few new girls come over the last couple of months who have
already done webcam
before. And I noticed that they made a profile of ours, a brand new profile.
But like I said,
they'd already done it before, but they were starting fresh reviews. So they
already had a lot
of knowledge about webcam. They were already successful before they came here.
So they had
some, you know, they had some knowledge of how to do it, good themselves. And
they actually
done a credit purchase at the very start of their webcam journey. So they paid
five, 10 or 20 pounds
and put that onto their profile. So then they used that five, 10 or 20 credits,
which I then
translated to, they used that to bid themselves on the front page to then get
calls to then generate
more money and get them, like basically get themselves, you know, get
themselves in the swing of things.
Because when you know, sometimes it can take, you know, it can take a bit
longer to get, become
successful and to become busy because obviously, you know, you're new, you're
waiting for people to
come in, you don't have any credit to put yourself on the front page. So it can
be a little bit
longer in the beginning, which is fine. You know, we've all been there and
spent that time waiting
and building it up. But if you don't want to wait to build it up and you don't
mind spending
five or 10 pounds, then you can literally just upload five pounds into your
profile,
use it to put yourself on the front page. Hopefully you get calls through, make
some more money from
that, which then you use a bit of that to put yourself on the front page, and
you make a bit
more and then, you know, it's just up and up and up from there, hopefully. Of
course, I can't guarantee
that. And I'm not saying that you need to spend your own money because this is
not something we've
ever recommended before. And it's not something that I'm saying you have to do.
Like I said,
I just noticed these girls doing it and it worked really well for them. They
made a lot
that month by doing this and they only done it once or twice at the start. And
then once they had
credits in their account, they didn't have to do it again because obviously
they had credits
then to use that every hour for the front page. So yes, that's something to
bear in mind. But yeah,
again, you don't have to do this. If you don't want to spend your own money on
this, that's absolutely
fine. You will make credits that you can use for the front page. But if you
want to do it faster,
this is a way. And it can work for sure. I've seen a lot of the all the credit
statements and
it definitely works. Okay, I'm going to scan through my list. I think I've got
one or two more and then
I'm going to hand over to the next person. Okay, so I'll just end with this
final one
because I think some of the others, some of the other girls I'm going to chat
about later.
And so my final tip is to just basically live in a state of gratitude. And I
know that's not
realistic all of the time, of course, but as much as possible, just come back
to gratitude and
especially for this job because, you know, we can literally open up our laptops
,
spend however long online. And then the next day, receive that money in our
bank. It's honestly,
like, it can honestly be a life changer for you if you put the time and energy
in. I can vouch
for that, Elle can vouch for that. I know Chloe can vouch for that Sophie too.
You know, we all
started exactly where you girls did on day one. Some of us didn't even have the
support of the
community around us. So it's even better with all the support and guidance. But
yeah, this can
honestly just, yeah, I just lose the words sometimes when I try to speak about
webcam because I'm just
so, so grateful for it. It's so amazing. And if we feel that way when we're
going on cam,
if we feel that high energy, we feel positive, you know, it will translate to
our clients,
we're putting that out there to the universe and putting out that good feeling
it's going to come
back to us. So yeah, just try and get yourself into a good mindset, get
yourself into feeling
really good about this before coming online, because I think that it really
does make the biggest
difference when, yeah, when you feel grateful about it, when you feel just, you
know, when you just
realise how amazing this is, I feel as though you attract so much more. So yes,
I will leave you
there. I think that's been about 10 minutes. We have to, we want to stick to
right now. I don't
rub it on anymore. But yeah, thanks for listening, girlies. I'll pass you once
at the next person.
Thank you, G. So we're going to go to Sophie. Oh, you weren't next anyway,
Sophie.
So we're going to go to Sophie next. So I'll pin you, Sophie.
Okay, sorry. There's a bit of background noise, is that okay?
Yeah, yeah, as long as you're okay. Yeah,
she's just being very, very clingy.
Yeah, I just got my notes on. I've heard the last bit of the call, but she was
just chatting away
through all of Welles and most of Georgia, sorry, but so sorry if I repeat
anything.
But the last bit of Georgia's ahead was amazing,
definitely about gratitude and like just living it and it's brilliant.
And yeah, I'm going to talk about phone chat and SMS. So I find it quite
lucrative because
you can just pop it on when you don't even have to get ready and people just
ring you
and you can be doing whatever. Everyone's seeing me like crocheting and talking
to you.
It's one, two, and then SMS chats. Similar, it's just texts. You can get texts
whenever.
They text you and then you get paid for every text that you send back.
You need to verify your mobile number on the site for all of this thing and
then set it up.
If you need a hand, you can message me another time. I won't go into it now,
unfortunately,
I haven't got too long to talk. But yeah, the phone chats, you stick it on and
then it goes
off every two hours so you just can pop it back on. And then there's a
brilliant thing that one of
our girls found on within the email section over on the right-hand side there's
a list and within
the list it says direct chat to call history. And it's basically like a list of
all equals,
whether you answered them or not, how long they were, who were hungry, like
every detail that
unnecessary details but it's really good. But you can click on their name and
email them straight
from that. So I've just had two missed calls. I'm gonna say even guy and I've
just clicked on
his name and emailed him back saying, "Oh sorry, ring me back late. I can't
talk right now, ring me
back later when you see me online." And you know, most of the times they do
ring you back,
especially when you get two, three, four missed calls from the same guy.
And because like Jay was saying, I did catch that bit about, you know, email
everyone.
Some people you can tell the time, wait, it's like someone's been emailing me,
he's literally
got minus one feedback. And the message is just awful and I'm just like, no, go
away. But apart from
that, it's great. And yeah, he's gonna message me with more questions. I've
anyone's got any
questions now while I'm actually free. Oh, bless you Sophie. Thank you so much
for coming on.
Bless you with a little one as well. All right, I just obviously wasn't
expecting
us to be up this late. She had a very late nap. Yeah, that's one of, it's one
of those things,
isn't it? As a parent, you never know. You never know what's gonna be going on
with them.
Yeah, well, I haven't tried this job so good. Very, very flexible.
Exactly, yeah, exactly. I either sleep or if I'm not too tired, I jump on cam.
And yeah, it's a nice little 50 quid for the next day or whatever. Sometimes
you get looking,
300, I did the other night. No 300 credits so it was about 150, whatever.
Yeah, that's amazing, amazing. Yeah, it's so nice to hear one of the people
have a good day as
well. It's just a bit of a boost to everyone else, isn't it? Okay, shall we
move on?
Yes, absolutely, I will move on. Before we do, Elle, that's great, thank you,
Sophie. Love you.
But yeah, SMS and phone is not something we talk about as much because
obviously,
you know, we'd say with a webcam agency, but I don't know if everybody knows
that you can do
everything, you can do SMS and phone chat as well. So thank you for sharing
that, Sophie.
Sophie is the queen of SMS and phone chat. So if anyone ever needs any tips or
advice,
just let us know. But yeah, it can be really good, Connor. So if I just said,
like in between
calm clients and stuff like that, it's just, and especially if you've got
little ones as well,
maybe you can't jump on cam all the time, but you can send a text message or
whatever else,
or even out to the phone. Obviously, if the little ones are young, we're enough
to not know what
you're saying. I mean, we're not enough to not know, I should say. So yeah, I
think it's a really good
one to just be able to use when you're not able to use webcam. Yeah, I'm sure.
Yeah.
Okay, let's move on to who do we have next? I think it's Chloe. It's some
beautiful pictures
of you there. Hi. I don't know, every single one of them was in, done with the
CC as well.
All our photo shoots. So I'm actually talking about something that I've only
just actually
started doing. So I've been doing calm for about three years, pretty much full
time for the past
till. And I used to just smash the regulars. I was okay. I never really had a
dry spell.
Everyone had to keep me afloat. But then recently, I'd say in the past nine to
a year,
I've went completely quiet. And I was really, really struggling while I was
just in waiting on
whatever page to actually get seen. So I do actually, like G says, I'm
featuring a go on the first page.
I do really think that does help. But when you'll work for long periods of time
, like me,
you don't want to have to spend every single hour, even though you're making it
back. Sometimes
it's like, Oh, I just want to keep me for a credit. So if it's a busy night for
me to credit. So I
started free chat. So we're, I mean, you can obviously ask any of us how to do
it if you can't
find it or you're struggling, but where you can change your price, there's a
little box at the top
and it says enable free preview. So the second you click that and then you
press start. Again,
if you're already logged on, it will log you out, but it'll just log you
straight back on again.
And then you'll be in free preview. Now, it normally only takes a couple of
seconds,
in my opinion, but sometimes you might be waiting a minute or so. And then
people will just start
entering the room. It's not the same as group or private. You don't have to
accept it. So also,
be careful as well. If no one's in your room and you think, Oh, I'll walk out.
Someone can enter at
any points and see that you're not there or see you're sitting in the
background. So they do just
come in without warning. Sometimes they'll say, Hey, sometimes they won't, but
basically the stage
is yours. So you can say anything you like really add, try and not do anything
too spicy,
depends on what obviously needs you've gone for just because you are not
getting paid for this
paper chat. But I've got some tips that work for me when you're actually in
free. I just thought
it was explained because obviously most people aren't know what free is and
what it'll look like.
So I've got here as one as big as invite in, and as much as a conversation as
you can be,
because some of them will be nervous, some of them will be shy, and they might
not always say
the first thing. So even if it's just a hi, how can I make your night better?
Hi, how is your day?
Good morning. If you're doing it in the morning, you can do it at any time.
Just be bubbly and
confident and inviting and especially if they're just saying some nice things
like, Oh, you look
lovely today. But like, Oh, thank you so much. I've done this with me here. Or
like, I'd like to see
you and see to see if you want to go to group or private. Just be really
confident. This is the
only way I can describe it because it shows it really does. And it's a really
good way
to show like, yeah, like, I am professional. I know what I'm doing. Even if you
don't,
like, if you act confident, that will like, oh, yeah, feel safe with her. She
will be fun or kinky.
She's flirty, whatever. So that is my first one. Something I always say,
actually, as well,
with free because I know free has got a bad reputation. And I used to have the
same thing until I fell
in love with it as well as you think I don't want to talk to them for free,
especially if you are
used to doing well and waiting and you think I'm not talking to them for free
like I'd rather
get paid. But I just always say, say, imagine you're buying something off Etsy
and your message,
the seller, and you say, will this fit my measurements or just any question
ever? And they reply to saying,
I'm not answering your question or engaging in conversation until you buy the
item first.
I wouldn't buy it. So just treat it like that. Like, just be kind. You don't
have to give anything
away. You don't have to show anything. It can just be a face. You don't even
have to be done up. You
can be certain your pyjamas or gym wear or anything. But just don't short
anything down.
Like try and still be nice and they can get cheeky or a little bit sassy out in
free because
they aren't paying yes. But just take a breath and just answer as nice as you
can. Give them an
inch. Don't let them obviously get away with too much. But give them an inch,
stay engaged in.
And then obviously at the end of the conversation, if it's been a couple of
minutes in use of chance,
then you can hit them with the, now shall we go to group or private. So I think
that's always
a good way to look at it is if you're trying to buy something yourself, if they
wouldn't talk to
you until after you paid for it, you'd feel a certain way as well. So just try
and it is hard
sometimes because they can be cheeky or just try and take a breath. But that
brings me to
me next points as well where take breaks with free. I think this is really,
really important.
If you're not getting calls quickly, I think it's one of them things that you
have to take
breaks for because they can just enter without warning. There has been times
when it's been really
busy. Well, I've 10 people all saying the same thing. Hi, how are you? What are
you wearing and
what do you do in group or private? And it's very, very exhausting. Like,
especially if you're
not getting the calls, obviously, if they are then taking you to private and
then you do in a show.
And then you're going back and free, then it's more motivating because you're
making money.
But sometimes if it's quiet, you will just get people in an house and it's so
easy to then
be in the wrong mindset for it and think, oh no, I'm not answering that or no,
I'm not doing that.
So I, what I do personally is I do 15 minutes on, I'm 15, or 15 to 30 off.
If I don't get a call, if I'm getting calls, I will stay in it. If I'm not, I
'll do 15 minutes.
If I don't get a single call and 15 minutes, I come out of three. And I'll stay
and wait. And so
if I get any calls, I'm still technically where I can, but I'll just take
myself out of three.
I'll go and do something. I'll go and have a drink. I'll come back and I'll
start again. And it's,
it's fun then, I think, because it's kind of like having little breaks. So you
think, oh,
I've got half now to myself. And then you get back on the mindset of doing it
again. So I think
that's really, really important, especially if you've never done three before
as well. It
can be overwhelming. So taking breaks is really, really important for that.
I think I've poor Lovense. So a Lovense, I swear by this anyway, but
especially in three,
I think Sophie's just got one as well. And it's been working really, really
well for her.
It pays for itself. So a Lovense is a toy that you can connect to elsewhere.
And you can set it up where if anyone tips you, it buzzes and you can set the
price of the tips.
You can have them like I have one like really, really loud, but it'll only go
off for like five
seconds. And then obviously I have one for the higher price and it'll go off
for a minute. And
you can also change the modes and they can all see that on their end in a call
like group or
private, but especially free. So some clients might be in there free or in your
free. I should
say, but they don't actually have many credits in the bank. They might not
actually have enough
credits to take you to private. So they'll spend the remaining just on tipping
yet and giving
you a little buzz to see your reaction. And I don't even use sounds in free and
it still works.
So they don't, it's not like they need to hear you or anything. They will just
buzz pretty much
without warning. And you've got to like obviously react to it and stuff. So
thank you, stay bubbling
and that normally then gets other people taking you to group or private because
they want to
carry on the show obviously. So I think that's really good. Even if it's just
one, two credits,
it's still something others to it. So I think that really goes in free, but
especially in general,
like it pays for itself. I think the cheapest one is around 60 pounds. And
on it, that's like just over minimum, just over 90 credits I think, isn't it?
It really well adds,
I think it's the best investment I've ever had. I make a lot of money off tips.
And it's also
another selling point as well. So you can say like it's awkward asking for tips
. And I get that
a lot especially of other members or even just other calm girls. They say, oh,
I don't know how
to ask for tips that tips that will feel ruined. But when you've got a toy, it
's a very easy
selling point because it's very easy to then say, oh, well, you can control
this if you like,
it only goes off. If you tip that, is that okay? I always give them the option.
And most of the
time, they say, yeah, keep it in. So I think that especially if you're
struggling, obviously, maybe
have a feel for the site first, I'd say. And then when you start getting used
to clients and
used to people coming into your room, I really would look into getting other
events, but it also
works really well with free. And the last thing I've got is do not do something
that makes you feel
uncomfortable. I think that goes with any type of whether it's free, whether it
's phone chats,
whether it's just normal group or private. Just really don't go over your own
boundaries
because it's very easy and free as well. Because as I can say, because the men
aren't paying
us, they can be a little bit more cheeky. So if they say, will you do this? If
I take you
to private and you don't want to do it, don't say, yeah, just to get the
private call, just say,
no, it's not worth it. Like, even if you end a couple of credits off that call,
it'll just make
you feel bad in size. I've done that a few times and it's just not worth it. So
just set your own
boundaries and just make sure you're okay. Don't only do things that you're
comfortable with and
I think that goes with all of it anyway, but especially in free because I think
it's easier
to get convinced because you're not making money yet. So I think they're very
good at being like,
but I'll tip you this and we'll go to private right now if you do this thing.
So just say,
no, sorry. I'm sure there's someone online that'll do that, but I'm not
comfortable with that.
I'm not fine. I think that's it. Yeah.
Thank you, Chloe. That was amazing. That was so good. Yeah, thank you. That was
really good.
It was great to learn about love-ence and a bit more about free chat. I know
you do so well with it.
So yeah, that was great. Thank you so much. Teacher then and free can work well
as well.
You can do both at the same time because a question I got actually recently was
,
will I lose my place if I bid to be on the front page? Because obviously, as I
said, when you go
in free, it locks your house and then back in again. You don't lose your place
on the front page.
You'll either just be in free or you'll come out of free so you won't lose your
place and
do both work amazingly together, one or the other. I normally pop in and I also
think if I'm
bidding for the front page, so that's something so. Thank you. Thank you so
much. Okay. Okay.
Me. Right, let me pin myself. Okay, so. Sorry, I just, I'm realising that I
have a new laptop,
ladies. So usually I'd be sharing this and I think it's like not sharing it the
best. But
never mind. It's only the tips that we need. So my top tip, so I was going to
talk about some other
stuff. Actually, I decided to talk more about, I guess, about understanding
yourself and understanding
your clients, because this is something that I've been talking with to members
about over the past
couple of weeks, because, you know, a few people they've had, you know, some
new people to come,
some people that have been with us for a couple of months or whatever, have got
in touch and just
wanted a little check in. And that, you know, been feeling maybe a little bit
anxious about
a few things, or just that, you know, a certain call might have made them feel
a certain way,
or that maybe feeling some resistance to going online at some times. So I
wanted to kind of talk
a little bit about this, because I think it's so important. And so the first
thing I wanted to
talk about is how I think they're so often when we're in this job, or
especially, you know,
newbies just starting out, we tend to think that because we are showing up and
it's, you know,
we're getting dressed up, we're showing up with, we're the ones that are like
in this little box
on the screen that people are looking at, we tend to think that we are the
product that we're selling.
So I think, you know, it can be easy to get your confidence knocked, or, you
know, for your self
esteem to get mixed up in, like what calls are getting or not getting. And, you
know,
you can feel a bit sort of anxious or a bit stressed when people come in and
out of your chat,
you know, very quickly, or someone leaves halfway, what you think is halfway
through a call. So this
stuff happens to all of us, you know, no matter how much of an expert you are,
how long you've been
doing it, we all get what we call peepers, which are people that come in and
out of your room very
quickly from a multitude of reasons, you know, they could, their wife could be
there,
they could be in work, they could have run out of credits, they could be
looking for something
specific, there's tons of reasons why this happens. So just understanding that
this is normal,
firstly, I think is really important. And I think it's also really important to
kind of reframe this
a little bit, because if we think that we are the products that we're selling,
then we're going to
feel like a knock to a confidence or whatever, when we're not making as much
money as we want to,
or we're not keeping all the calls or whatever. So rather than thinking of it
that way, that it's
you or the product that you're selling, it's not you, it's the relationship. So
what that means is,
rather than it being about your looks or your personality, or anything to do
with you as an
individual, it's about how you're making them feel. It's about what dynamic you
can create together
with your client. And it's about a story and a fantasy, because that's what
this is at the end
of the day is all fantasy. They're coming here and stepping outside of their
normal life and coming
to this place of fantasy. So and the reason they're doing that is because they
want to feel a certain
way, or they want to talk about certain things. They want someone who can be
with them in this
fantasy. And that is where we, that for me at least, this is kind of what my
specialty, I guess,
is where I find it can be really, really lucrative. And I think a lot of the
girls who do
make the most money on cam, they make that money because they can build
relationships with their
clients, they can really engage them, make them feel good, and tune into what
it is the client
actually wants, not as invite what to do for them, but how they want to feel
like what kind of
relationship they want. So I think, so it, so changing the narrative slightly,
it's not you
you're selling, you're selling an experience. So how do you make that
experience, Beth, you know,
the best experience it can be for them. So they're going to want to come back
and become a regular
hopefully and stay for a long time and make lots of money, make you lots of
money.
I think that some ways to do this are to have little stories. And I've talked
about this on many
calls, really, and have some little stories that you've practiced that you can
tell clients.
So you can have a lohon, Reddit, or there's loads of like fantasy writing
things online,
loads of stories you can read for inspiration. Just have little things that
little stories that
you've got in your mind that you can bring out might be good, like when Chloe
is saying about,
you know, trying to engage with a little bit of this or that, something small,
like, you know,
I saw my neighbor today and I really fancy them, they're really hot, or I've
just ordered a toy,
and you know, somebody else has taken the delivery for me, I wonder what's
going to happen.
Or I went to the doctor's today, like the doctor was hot, like little sexy
stories,
just about your day, or maybe I went to buy some underwear today, or tell them
about something
you're wearing, or I went on a date last night, like little things, it can
really help you
firstly feel like you've got something to say, and secondly, help you to give
them the experience,
you know, which is what they're here for, the fantasy and the experience.
Another thing to be mindful of, if you're thinking about selling the experience
, as I'm saying,
is one, you know, one thing to do, if you're feeling like, just one thing to
keep in your mind
all the time, I think is really useful, is just to be curious, like just be
curious about anything
they're bringing, you know, if they tell you something, whatever they tell you,
just being
curious about it, oh, what does that mean for you, or how does that feel for
you, or when's the first
time you realise that you liked such and such, like just asking open questions
and being curious,
like, allows them to open up, and then you can get to know more about what they
like,
and when you know more about what they like, you can give them a better
experience,
so curiosity, I think, is like a really underrated tip, and especially because
maybe a lot of new
people can feel the pressure to act like they know everything, but actually, if
you know everything,
you're not being curious with the person that's in front of you, so it's much
better to be curious,
and if you don't know a word they said, or whatever, just ask, you know,
curiosity, they love it,
so just stay curious. A couple of things about keeping yourself safe, and
keeping yourself
comfortable, because as Chloe said, those things are really important, so just,
I think, understanding,
and this came to life after a conversation I had in the last couple of weeks
with a member,
where, you know, I realised it's so important to point out that just because
you've done something
once doesn't mean that you have to do it again, or because you've done
something once that you
have to do it with the next customer, or the next customer, consent doesn't
mean that you decide
what your boundaries are, and then you do that with every person every time,
like you have the power,
you have the control for what you're doing, and if you're feeling uncomfortable
, or rubbish about
what you're doing, you can start at any time, you can say that, you know, I'm
not so into this,
or you can just kick them out, or you can just close your laptop, you know, you
're always in
control of what you're doing, and when you feel that sense of like being in
control, I think that
a lot of the time it lets you relax a little bit, so you can be more open with
your clients,
and you can be more connected with them a bit better, because then you're not
feeling really
uptight about the stuff you're going to have to do that you've already decided,
so yeah, just knowing
that consent is not fixed, like it's fluid, it changes all the time, and
sometimes you might want
to do something with one client, and you don't want to do it with the next one,
and you don't even
have to know why someone's energy is enough, you know, sometimes you might
think I'm just going to
do this today, because I'm not feeling it, and then you start trying to decline
that, or you really
connect with them feel amazing with, so you actually end up doing more of them,
and that's cool as well.
One thing that Chloe mentioned, like touched on slightly that I'll hone in on a
bit more, is
about not just saying no, like so often I hear like members, which is great,
obviously, like this
is you managing your consent saying no to someone, but what I find is better is
if you can turn your
no into a question, or is if you can turn it into a story, like I haven't done
that yet, but
you know, I'm interested in finding out about this, or oh no, I'm not, you know
, you can still say no,
but you're just turning it into a conversation, rather than saying no, and that
's it, there's no
way to go from there, is there other than end the call, so just if a client
asks you something
or talks about something and you're not sure, just ask them about it, just be
curious about it,
and it's okay to say I'm not sure, I haven't done that before, I don't know,
like don't know if I
would want to do that, like tell me about it, you know, ultimately you're just
having a back and
forth, and the longer you can have a back and forth with your client, the
better, so it's okay to
ask them questions, even if you're not sure you want to go down that road, you
can still ask them
about it. Yeah, so I think that's, I think that's it really, I think it's just
remembering that
it's not you that you're selling, it's an experience, and having a few stories
in your back pocket,
and then when you figure out what your client is kind of after, how they want
to feel or what
they're into, then you can just amend those stories that you've got to fit them
, so you can just, you
know, if you've got a few things that you remember, a few stories that you tell
, you can keep telling
them, I've probably told the same stories millions times, and then when you get
the great clients,
they'll start building on your stories and reflecting back to you, and then
they can be really long
calls, so yeah, just remembering that it's a fantasy, and that you are not the
product,
it's just connecting with your clients that will make you money. So I think
that's it from me,
did we have something? Oh, it's just so close in by in the chat,
might be a question, does anyone have any questions or anything up to this
point for any others?
No, feel free to share in the chat or speak up if you want to see something.
Thank you, Paula, it was really good to see you. So the only one we got left is
Sammy, so Sammy
was travelling back from somewhere, we weren't sure whether she was going to
make it or not,
so it was like she's not going to make it, but one of us, she has sent us her
tips, so we can read
out the tips. Let me see, but Sammy, okay, so I think it might be a lot of
similar things,
but let's see, Sammy's top tips were, so, and as Chloe was saying, a genuine
smile,
so a warm, genuine smile can go a long way, positive self-talk, so starting
your day with
affirmations, to boost your confidence, to help you stay focused and friendly,
again, similar to what Chloe was saying, just managing your own energy and
feeling good,
obviously that reflects what doesn't it to your clients. Active listening, so
pay attention to
what your clients are saying, preferably and non-verbally, if you can see, if
you can see them,
this shows that you value their thoughts and care about their needs, so yeah,
just being
tuned into your clients, which I think if we're like the stuff I was saying
about consent and about
like just making sure you're comfortable, knowing you're not the product, you
know,
once you can manage those things, then you don't need to be uptight and like,
you know, a bit stressed
and managing yourself, you can just relax into it, and then you can just focus
more fully on the client,
you know, body language, to Sami saying about maintaining open and approachable
body language,
such as uncrossing your arms, sitting up straight, conveying confidence and
friendliness,
so that's really important. Gratitude, George was saying that, as well, mindful
presence,
so try to be present in the moment and fully engage with your clients, so
keeping distractions,
away when you're working and focusing on the conversation. Positive energy, Sam
i's talking about
positive energy from people around you, so trying to surround yourself with
positive influences
and people who lift you up, obviously there's many of those people on this
group, like Elaine,
if you're struggling, then posting in the groups, the WhatsApp groups, or
reaching out to someone for
support and self-care, so taking care of your physical and mental well-being,
Sami says, "When you feel good, you're more likely to project a positive and
welcoming
attitude towards clients, take time for breaks if you need to, try not to go
online if you're
feeling bad or in a bad mood, take care of yourself first and make sure you
feel better before going
online because you want to project your best self." And of course, she's saying
, always reach out,
you know, to any of us if you need help with your mindset, because Sami finds
she does really well
if she's feeling confident and positive, and that reflects in the earnings with
her clients.
Of course, clients want to engage with someone who is genuine and who's happy
and positive as well,
especially when they're coming to you for a fantasy, so they're coming to you
to feel good.
So I think that that is ours. Does anybody have any questions or anything? I
don't think that
they'd like to ask really, it just has to be about top tips, and then we've got
a couple of new
newbies here. So anything you'd like to ask any of us while we're here?
Or even if anyone wants to share any of their own top tips, if anyone's got
anything naturally
being helping them on camera recently? No? Oh, thank you, Mario, saying. "A
London photo shoot,
yeah, good question." Yes, yes, there will be a summer London photo shoot. I
have been trying to
figure this out for the past couple of weeks, so I've just been back and
forward photographers and
venue and stuff. Yes, it's been a bit tricky to get them all aligned, but yeah,
that will be
happening, so I'll post in the group as soon as I can get everything aligned,
and I'll let you know.
And yeah, I don't think we've got our next dates out yet. I have a word for our
next calls, but we'll
post those in the chat as soon as we've got them. Yeah, it's a great idea to
come to one of the
shoots. Mario, it's good to get new photos, and it's just a nice chance to meet
some people as well
and have a lovely day, so yeah, we'll have to be good to see you on the next
shoot.
Okay, ladies, well good luck to anyone who's going online after this. I hope
you all have a
lovely week, and we'll see you very soon. Thank you everyone, thanks for coming
. Hi ladies, see you.